

Martin Bernabe Morcos Raiden

- bernabemorcos@gmail.com
- in bernabe-morcosr
- U02C5HKNEP3

- bernamr
- 3517611878
 - 😲 Catamarca, Argentina

PROFILE

With a degree in Economy, I decided to do a change my career. Last year I started my gastronomic project. This entrepreneurship allows me to develop management abilities such as creating a product, selling it using marketing, and managing with employees. In the past 2 years, I have been studying data science and after completing a 24-week intensive coding Bootcamp, I am seeking a data scientist position where I can contribute with my knowledge experience.

EDUCATION

Bootcamp In Data Science, *Le Wagon* 02/2022

Bachelor Degree in Economy,

National University of Córdoba. 12/2018

Data Science Specialization with Python,

Coursera, Michigan State Univesity. 06/2020

Certification in Machine Learning,

Coursera, Stanford University. 03/2020

Certificate in Business Intelligence,

Siglo XXI University 03/2020 – 09/2020

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Founder and Manager of Café Solo, Café Solo

03/2021 - present

Purchasing executive, BG CONS

03/2017 - 07/2019

Main task: Deal with suppliers in order to supply materials and equipment for the construction site.

PROJECTS

Al Diabetic Retinopathy Assistant 🔗

02/2022

The final project of the Le Wagon Bootcamp. AI DR assistant is supporting doctors by the use of Deep Learning technology and images prediction. This platform allows users to have a preliminary diagnosis of the degree of the disease.

SKILLS

| Python | • | • | • | • | |
|--------------|---|---|---|---|--|
| Sklearn | • | • | • | • | |
| Github | • | • | • | | |
| Google Cloud | • | • | • | | |
| R | • | • | | | |
| Docker | • | • | • | | |
| SQL | • | • | • | | |
| keras | • | • | • | | |
| Pandas | • | • | • | • | |

LANGUAGES

English First Cortificate B

First Certificate B2

INTERESTS

- Music: guitar player
- Sports: football, cycling, running.
- Reading